let questions = [
{
	numb: 1,
	question: "	Who developed Python Programming Language?",
	answer: "Guido van Rossum",
	options: [
	"Wick van Rossum",
	"Rasmus Lerdorf",
	"Guido van Rossum",
	" Niene Stom"
	]

},
{
	numb: 2,
	question: "Which type of Programming does Python support?",
	answer: " all of the mentioned",
	options: [
	"object-oriented programming",
	"structured programming",
	"functional programming",
	" all of the mentioned"
	]

},
{
	numb: 3,
	question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
	answer: "No",
	options: [
	"Yes",
	"No",
	"Machine dependent",
	"None of the above"
	]

},
{
	numb: 4,
	question: "Is Python code compiled or interpreted?",
	answer: "Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
	options: [
	"Python code is both compiled and interpreted",
	"Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
	"Python code is only compiled",
	"Python code is only interpreted"
	]

},
{
	numb: 5,
	question: " Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?",
	answer: "Indentation",
	options: [
	"Indentation",
	"Key",
	"Brackets",
	"All of Mentioned"
	]

},
{
	numb: 6,
	question: " Which of the following is the truncation division operator in Python?",
	answer: "//",
	options: [
	"|",
	"}",
	"//",
	"*"
	]

},
{
	numb: 7,
	question: " Which of the following is true for variable names in Python?",
	answer: "unlimited length",
	options: [
	"underscore and ampersand are the only two special characters allowed",
	"unlimited length",
	"all private members must have leading and trailing underscores",
	"None of Mentioned"
	]

},
{
	numb: 8,
	question: " What does pip stand for python",
	answer: "Preferred Installer Program",
	options: [
	"Unlimited length",
	"All private members must have leading and trailing underscores",
	"Preferred Installer Program",
	"none of the mentioned"
	]

},
{
	numb: 9,
	question: " What is the order of precedence in python?",
	answer: "Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction",
	options: [
	"Exponential, Parentheses, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction",
	"Exponential, Parentheses, Division, Multiplication, Addition, Subtraction",
	"Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Subtraction, Addition",
	"Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction"
	]

},
{
	numb: 10,
	question: " Which of the following functions can help us to find the version of python that we are currently working on?",
	answer: "sys.version(1)",
	options: [
	"sys.version(0)",
	"sys.version(1)",
	"sys.version(2)",
	"sys.version"
	]

},

];